cheeserank.com 2017-06-16

# PRIVACY POLICY This policy was last modified on March 25, 2015.

                                            PRIVACY POLICY
This policy was last modified on March 25, 2015.
The web site you have entered (CheeseRank.com, its sub-domains and any services available
therefrom, including any mobile versions of the web site or mobile applications) (the “Site”) is
operated by VaynerStudios, LLC (“VaynerStudios,” “we” or “us”). We respect the your privacy rights
and recognize the importance of protecting information collected from you and about you. This
privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) describes how we collect, use, and share that information. Your
use of the Site constitutes your acceptance of this Privacy Policy.
1.     Collection of Information
       a.      We collect personally identifiable information when you voluntarily provide it to
us.
We collect personally identifiable information from you in several different ways on the Site.
Personally identifiable information means information that can reasonably used to identify you
personally, such as your name, username(s), birth date, phone number, and email address).We
collect such information when you voluntarily provide it to us (such as when you complete an online
account registration, subscription form, contest or sweepstakes entry or comment submission). You
can choose not to provide the requested information, but you might not be able to take advantage
of certain Site features.
       b.      We automatically collect information about your browser or device, your use of
the Site, and your browsing or search history when you interact with us.
       When you access and use the Site, our technology and tools automatically collect and record
certain non-personally identifiable information about your use of the Site (including your IP address,
your browser type, the make and model of device used to view the Site, location information, unique
device identifiers, and other information relating to your use of the Site, browser or device).
       We also use cookies, pixels, web beacons, device or HTML5 local storage and caching, java
script and other similar technologies to collect information about your use of and access to the Site,
content or advertisements you view, and related to your activities on the Internet. Cookies are small
bits of information that may be placed on your computer by web sites you visit, applications you
use, or advertisements you view. Cookies alone tell us nothing about who you are, unless you or a
third-party gives us personally identifiable information, which may then be linked to the data stored
in the cookie. Pixels (or pixel tags, web beacons or clear GIFs) are small blocks of code placed on a
web page or application that read and place cookies and transmit certain information, such as a
browser or device’s IP address, when and how often the pixel was viewed, an identifier associated
with the browser or device, or the type of browser being used.
       c.      Third-parties may also automatically collect information about you.
       Some advertisements or embedded content on the Site are served by third-party advertising
companies or third-party content providers. Please note that these companies may also use cookies
or other similar technologies to collect information about you, both on the Site and throughout the
Internet. We do not have control over third-party information collection and use.

       d.      We may build a profile about you based on information you voluntarily provide
us, information we automatically collect from you, and information obtained from third-
parties.
       We may combine information provided by or collected from you in connection with your use
of the Site with information provided by you to us in other ways, information we obtain from third-
party market researchers, information provided to us via your use of social media platforms, public
information or other third-party information sources.
2.     Use of Collected Information
We collect and use the types of information described above to assist in the administration and
operation of the Site and to provide you an efficient, meaningful, and customized experience. We
may use the information to:
    •  Fulfill our obligations with respect to reason you volunteered the information (e.g., to
       respond to an inquiry, administer a contest or sweepstakes, deliver a newsletter, etc.);
    •  Allow you to participate in interactive features of the Site;
    •  Deliver marketing, advertising, and promotional messages to you;
    •  Improve the Site or our products and services;
    •  Optimize your experience on the Site (e.g., troubleshooting technical programs, storing your
       preferences, etc.);
    •  Show you relevant Site content and advertising on and off the Site, and analyze Site content
       and advertising;
    •  Notify you about changes to the Site or our services (including this Privacy Policy); and
    •  Carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from arrangements between you and
       us.
3.     Advertising
We use collected information to serve relevant, customized advertising to you. Such advertising (and
analysis of advertising) may be conducted by us or third-parties. Your information may be shared
with third-parties for advertising delivery, contextual advertising and reporting on such advertising.
Generally, these third-parties do not have the right to use this information beyond the scope needed
to execute or support advertising.
Some advertisers and services we use to deliver advertising may be engaging in online behavioral
advertising and interest-based advertising. You can read more about online behavioral, interest-
based advertising, and related practices here:
    • Network Advertising Initiative
    • Digital Advertising Alliance
    • Interactive Advertising Bureau
4.     Third-Party Websites and Third-Party Embedded Content.
We do not control the privacy policies of third-party web sites, our affiliates, and business partners
which may be accessed, directly or indirectly, through your use of the Site. Any information you
provide to, or that is collected by, third-party sites may be subject to the privacy policies of those

sites (including third-party content embedded on the Site), if any. It is up to you to review the terms
of use and privacy policy of third-party websites or third-party content originators.
5.      How We Share Information
        a.     Partners and Service Providers. We may provide collected information to our
business partners, clients, licensees, and service providers. They may use your information to
perform services for us and advertise their products and services to you.
        b.     Advertisers or Advertising Networks. We may provide collected information (either
alone or combined with information provided by third-parties or public information) about users of
the Site on an aggregated, anonymous basis to our advertisers to help them reach the kind of
audience they want to target.
        c.     Law Enforcement and Safety. We may also share or disclose your information to
comply with a court order or other legal obligation, to enforce the Site terms of use, and to protect
the rights, property or safety of our users and other third-parties. We may disclose information to
government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we determine, in our sole and absolute
discretion, is necessary or appropriate to respond to claims or to comply with legal processes, to
comply with laws, regulations or ordinances or to prevent or stop illegal, unethical or actionable
activity.
        d.     Business Transfer. In the event that the Site or VaynerStudios undergoes a merger,
acquisition by another company or sale of its assets (including the Site), your information will, in
most instances, be part of the assets transferred.
6.      Opting-Out of Information Use
As described above, we collect personally identifiable information about you when you voluntarily
provide it to us, collect other information about you and your use of the Site automatically when you
interact with us, and may combine the collected information with publicly available information or
information provided to us by third-parties or to build a profile about you. If you do not want us to
use your collected information as described above or to provide your information to our partners,
clients or service providers for marketing purposes, please email us with such request.
With respect to the Site’s use of cookies and other similar technologies, by adjusting settings on
your browser, you may elect not to allow cookies to be placed, and thus opt out of certain features
of the Site and the Site’s automatic collection of certain information about you.
Additionally, the links below will assist you in opting-out of cookies and online behavioral or
interest-based advertising:
    • First-Party Opt-Out:
            o Visit Google: http://www.google.com/privacy/ads
            o Click “Ads Settings”
    • Third-Party and Online Behavioral Advertising Opt-Out
            o Please visit:
                  § Digital        Advertising       Alliance         Consumer      Choice       Page:
                      http://www.aboutads.info/choices
                  § Network           Advertising          Initiative       Consumer          Opt-Out:

                     http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/
Please note that these measures are browser-specific and device-specific and must be repeated on
all browsers and devices.
7.      Protection of Information
We use reasonable measures to safeguard your information in our possession. However, no data
transmission over the Internet is completely secure and no security mechanism is impenetrable.
Therefore, although we take steps to protect your information, we cannot guarantee the security of
the information that we collect from you or the security of our servers or the Site. By accessing the
Site, any transmission of information is at your own risk and you agree to assume all risk in
connection with information sent to us or collected by us.
8.     User Contributions.
You are responsible for content that you contribute to be published or displayed on the Site or
transmit to other users of the Site (“User Contributions”), if any. Your User Contributions are posted
on and transmitted to other users of the Site at your own risk. Additionally, we cannot control the
actions of other users of the Site with whom you may choose to share your User Contributions.
Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that your User Contributions will not be viewed by
unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security
measures contained on the Site. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies
of your User Contributions may remain viewable in cached or archived pages or might have been
copied or stored by others.
9.      Foreign Jurisdiction.
The Site is designed for and targeted to United States audiences and are governed by and operated
in accordance with the laws of the United States. VaynerStudios is not responsible under any privacy
laws or local data protection laws in any jurisdiction other than the United States.
10.    Children and Parents.
We respect children’s privacy. We do not target or knowingly or intentionally collect personally
identifiable information from children under the age of 13. By using the Site, you have represented
and warranted that you are either 18 years of age or using the Site with the supervision of a parent
or guardian. If you are under the age of 13, you may not use the Site. If you become aware that your
child has provided us with personal information without your consent, please email us.
If you are a California resident under the age of 18 and a registered user of the Site, California
Business and Professions Code Section 22581 permits you to request and obtain removal of content
or information you have publicly posted, including User Submissions. To make such a request,
please email us or write us with a detailed description of the specific content or information to be
removed.
Please be aware that such a request does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of the
content or information you have posted (including User Submissions, if any) and that there may be
circumstances in which the law does not require or allow removal even if requested.

11.     Your California Privacy Rights
If you are a California resident, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits you to request
information regarding the disclosure of your personal information by VaynerStudios to third-parties
for direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please email us or write us.
12.     Miscellaneous.
From time to time VaynerStudios may modify this Privacy Policy to reflect, among other things,
changes in the law or our information collection and use practices and such modifications shall be
effective upon posting by VaynerStudios. Your continued use of the Site after a revised Privacy Policy
signifies your acceptance of the revised Privacy Policy. It is important that you review this Privacy
Policy regularly to ensure you are updated as to any changes.
13.     Contact Us.
If you have any general questions about this Privacy Policy or other aspects of the Site please contact
us at:
VaynerStudios
Attention: CheeseRank.com Privacy Policy
315 Park Avenue South, 16th Floor New York, NY 10010, USA or Email: contact@VaynerStudios.com
If you are making a request related to your rights as a resident of California, please contact us at:
VaynerStudios
Attention: CheeseRank.com California Privacy Rights
315 Park Avenue South, 16th Floor New York, NY 10010, USA or Email: contact@VaynerStudios.com
with Subject Line: California Privacy Rights
You also may have the right (subject to certain exceptions) to be given a copy of the information
that we collects about you or to correct, update, and/or erase that information. Please email us with
any such request.
